{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The condition of a part when it contains the least amount of material is referred to as ________.", "opta": "smallest", "optb": "LMC", "optc": "MMC", "optd": "actual size", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This is used to indicate that a surface is to be machined:", "opta": "Finish mark", "optb": "Machining mark", "optc": "Roughness indicator", "optd": "Coordinate mark", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ________ tool on the Dimension tool bar places the length of an arch on a drawing.", "opta": "Arc Radius", "optb": "Arc Length", "optc": "Radius", "optd": "Diameter", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How can the drafter prevent AutoCAD from placing or stacking another center mark on a circle when adding a diameter dimension to it?", "opta": "Explode the dimension and then erase the center mark.", "optb": "Use the Properties dialog box to turn off the center mark of the dimension.", "optc": "It can't be done.", "optd": "Use the trim tool to take away the stacked center mark.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In this type of dimensioning, allowance must be made for bends:", "opta": "Angular", "optb": "Tolerance", "optc": "Datum", "optd": "Sheet metal", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One way to evenly space dimensions on a drawing is to use the ________.", "opta": "Dimension Space tool", "optb": "Linear tool", "optc": "Continue tool", "optd": "Baseline tool", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ________ tool on the Dimension tool bar will place several dimensions at one time by using a selection box placed over several part features.", "opta": "Linear", "optb": "Continue", "optc": "Baseline", "optd": "Quick Dimension", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A circular arc is dimensioned in the view where you see its true shape by giving the value for its:", "opta": "Diameter", "optb": "Arc length", "optc": "Radius", "optd": "Chord length", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This is the total amount that the feature on the actual part is allowed to vary from what is specified by the dimension:", "opta": "Allowance", "optb": "Tolerance", "optc": "Specification", "optd": "Difference", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ________ dimension tool will place the length of an angled line.", "opta": "Aligned", "optb": "Angle", "optc": "Linear", "optd": "Radial", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Placement of dimensions on a drawing is controlled by ________.", "opta": "ANSI", "optb": "The design engineer", "optc": "Corporate drafting standards", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Baseline dimensions are referenced from a common geometric feature known as a ________.", "opta": "edge", "optb": "corner", "optc": "datum", "optd": "point of reference", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Given a situation in which the drafter has crossed extension lines in a drawing what can be done to clean up the point of crossing?", "opta": "Use the Modify tool to clean up the extension lines.", "optb": "Use the Tolerance tool to clean up the extension lines.", "optc": "Use the Break tool to clean up the extension lines.", "optd": "Use the stretch tool to clean up the extension lines.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This is a thin solid line directing attention to a note or dimension and starting with an arrowhead or dot:", "opta": "Dimension line", "optb": "Extension line", "optc": "Leader", "optd": "Specification", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The maximum and minimum sizes of a feature are identified by a ________ tolerance.", "opta": "Limits", "optb": "GD&T;", "optc": "reference", "optd": "allowance", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This is a line terminated by arrowheads, indicating the direction and extent of a dimension:", "opta": "Dimension line", "optb": "Extension line", "optc": "Arrowhead line", "optd": "Centerline", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In U.S. structural and architectural drafting, all dimensions of this length are usually expressed in feet and inches:", "opta": "One inch or over", "optb": "One foot or over", "optc": "One yard or over", "optd": "One rod or over", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}